happymorn.com 2009-03-20

# 

                                   Privacy Policy
Introduction
1. Thank you for taking the time to review our Privacy Policy. At times, This Proxy
hence forth referred to as TP will collect certain personal information about customers
and visitors to websites hosted by us. Such information will include non-identifiable
personal information. Non-identifiable information is gathered automatically when you
visit our website or those websites hosted by us, and stored for use in our system.
2. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what types of information
we will collect and how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this
information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the
most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we
are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Except where the
law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data.
Confidentiality
3. TP respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our website, or those
websites hosted by us. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and
users. We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial
or marketing purposes.
Collection of Personal Data
4. TP collects personal data about our users when you visit a website hosted by us; and
through the use of cookie technology. We may also combine information about you that
we have with information we obtain from our business partners or affiliates.
Use of Personal Data
5. TP may collect and share aggregated user data with business partners, sponsors or
other third parties for the purposes of developing content and ensuring relevant
advertising and content, such user data will never be used to identify individual users.
These business partners and affiliated companies do not have any independent right to
share this information.
6. TP may log the websites you visit; collect IP addresses and information about your
operating system and the type of browser you use for the purposes of network/system
administration; to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of
our site. This data however will not be used to identify individual users who will at all
times remain anonymous.

7. Any information TP collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via e-
mail, telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within
that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence within IF or to a third
party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the
point necessary to address your query or concerns, and will otherwise be kept
confidential.
Public Space (Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third-Party Sites)
8. Any information that customers disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin
board, chat room or any site TP may host for you, is available to anyone else who visits
that space. TP cannot safeguard any information you disclose there.
Site Linking
9. TP's websites contain many links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to us. TP
cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you
disclosing personal such information on third party sites. TP cannot protect any
information you may disclose on these sites and recommends that you review the privacy
policy statements of those sites you visit.
General
10. TP reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required in good
faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal
claims.
11. TP further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate
or prevent illegal activities being committed over our network.
12. TP reserves our rights to disclose your personal information where you have given us
explicit legal written consent to do so.
13. TP reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes
and prevent any unauthorized attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our
property.
14. TP reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it without
further notification. It may be necessary to from time to time, check TP's privacy policy
for changes. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have
read the changes or updates as the case may be.
                  Originally used by Unblock Myspace and Myspace Proxy and How to make a proxy
